<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="appName">Local Train Booking</string>
    <string name="payment_method_image">Payment Method Image</string>


    <string name="select_seat">Select Seat</string>

    <!-- Array of available seats -->
    <string-array name="seats_array">
        <item>Seat A1</item>
        <item>Seat A2</item>
        <item>Seat A3</item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- Prompt for selecting a train -->
    <string name="select_train">Select Train</string>
    <string name="select_station">Select Station</string>

    <!-- Array of available trains -->
    <string-array name="trains_array">
        <item>Train XYZ</item>
        <item>Train ABC</item>
        <item>Train DEF</item>
        <!-- Add more train options as needed -->
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="station_array">
        <item>Pretoria</item>
        <item>Midrand</item>
        <item>Centurion</item>
        <item>Malboro</item>
        <item>sadton</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="about_train_booking">
        <![CDATA[
        Welcome to our Train Booking App!

        Our mission is to provide you with a seamless and convenient way to book train tickets for your journeys. Whether you are commuting daily or planning a long-distance trip, our app is designed to make your travel experience hassle-free and enjoyable.

        Key Features:
        - Easy Booking: Quickly search for trains, select your preferred seats, and book tickets with just a few taps.
        - Comprehensive Information: Get detailed information about train schedules, routes, fares, and available seats.
        - Secure Payments: Enjoy secure payment options and receive instant booking confirmations for your peace of mind.
        - User-Friendly Interface: Our app is designed with a user-friendly interface for smooth navigation and seamless ticket booking.
        - Personalized Experience: Save your favorite routes, view booking history, and receive personalized recommendations based on your travel preferences.

        About Us:
        We are a dedicated team passionate about simplifying your travel experience. Our goal is to provide reliable and efficient train booking services, ensuring that you can travel comfortably and confidently.

        Contact Us:
        If you have any questions, feedback, or need assistance, please don\'t hesitate to contact our support team at support@trainbookingapp.com. We\'re here to help you have a great journey!

        Thank you for choosing our Train Booking App. Happy travels!
        ]]>
    </string>


</resources>